（唯の鼻歌）
（唯）ふッ　う…
はあ～…　お～し！
Let's do this!
Onee-chan, be careful.
（憂）お姉ちゃん　気をつけてね
うん！
Thanks.
Well, see ya.
じゃあ　行ってきま～す！
行ってらっしゃい
Later.
ほッ　ほッ　ほッ　ほッ　ほッ…　あッ
おばあちゃん
おはよう！
Good morning, 'Ma.
My, Yui-chan.
（とみ）あ～ら　唯ちゃん
今日は早いのねえ
You're early today.
Yeah, I thought I'd do my best at life.
とにかく一生懸命
頑張ろうと思ってね
I'm glad to hear that.
あら　偉いわねえ
えへへッ
行ってくるね～！
Bye!
ほッ　ほッ　うッ！
ほッ…
あらあら…
My, my...
ほッ　ほッ　ほッ　ほッ…
・～
Shoot! We can't stop! We won't stop!
Singing out loud all day long!
We'll all take the chance to
jump up and make a wish,
and shout out
about our fun lives!
If we mess up, let's pretend it's a rehearsal and redo it!
Everyone has their own little cosmos which we call "heart."
It's tightly packed with emotions and love.
We're busy getting excited, blue, or in-between.
It's chaos every day, so might as well make a song out of it!
And sing all about it!
We unconsciously study music even in class.
We can start making rhythms with air guitars!
It's the feeling that counts!
Imagining the beats, we'll enjoy ourselves freely!
You lose if you can't have fun!
Sorry! We can't let go! We won't let that go!
Swinging around in every possible way like crazy girls,
we'll hit whatever note we want to!
Maybe groove a little like that, and reverb like so.
We want to try everything, until we die.
We'll chase tomorrow together,
dream a little when we take a break.
Let's be bold and faithful and shake this stage up a bit!
Once you feel the ovation, you can't get enough of it!
One, two...
Go!
Where dreams come true.
ほッ　ほッ　ほッ　ほッ　ほッ　ほッ…
はッ　はッ　はッ…
Hey, here she comes.
（律）おッ　来た来た
ほッ　ほッ　ほッ　ほッ…
（紬）青春って感じ～
遅刻ギリギリ…
This is what they call youth.
She's going to be late.
（和）唯～　早く～！
Yui, hurry up!
「早く」の意味が
わかってない！
Does she not understand what that means?
Finals!
は～あ～…　ギリギリセーフ
Barely on time.
また寝坊か？
Did you sleep in again?
早起きして
ジョギングしてたんだよね
I woke up early and went jogging.
So that's why you were late.
（澪）それで遅れたのか…
I also wrote "I'll do my best" on the senior questionnaire.
進路調査表に
「頑張る」って書いたしね～
Yeah, fight on!
（紬）うん　頑張って！
無意味に励ますなよ　ムギ
Mugi, don't give her unnecessary complements.
Wait, finals are coming up.
確かに　もうすぐ期末試験だしな
Already?
もう…？
I'm going on a tangent here, but Oguri Tadamasa achieved many admirable...
え～　余談ですが
小栗忠順の功績は　大変大きく…
She's already sound asleep.
〈早速　居眠り…〉
う～に～…
何を
どう頑張ると？
So tell me, what are you going to "do your best" at?
ちゃんと勉強します！
I will study!
おおッ
うん？
Mugi-chan, your notes are so pretty.
ムギちゃん
きれいに書いてるねえ
欲しい…
あとで　コピーとる？
I want.
Want me to make a copy for you later?
Thanks!
ありがと～
あ…　う…
あッ　澪ちゃんのノート
かわいいね～
Mio-chan, your notebook's so cute!
うるさい…
ウフ…　うん？
Shut up.
Ricchan, I see you were also sleeping during class.
りっちゃん
おぬしも授業中　居眠りを…
心の友よ…
You're definitely my soul mate.
う～ん…
頭が「た」で　真ん中が「き」
最後が「ん」…
It starts with a 't', then there's a 'k' some-
where in the middle, and it ends with an 'n'.
Here's a hint: it's edible.
ヒント　食べ物です
たぬきうどん
Tanuki udon.
え？　それ
どういう食べ物？
What type of dish is that?
丸ごと入ってるんだよ　たぬき
わあ…
There's a raccoon in it, and it's intact.
全然　勉強に
ならないじゃないか
We're not getting any studying done.
うん？　おッ
ふう…
ムギちゃん　ありがとね
ううん
Mugi-chan, thanks.
You're welcome.
唯　ムギ
（２人）うん？
Yui! Mugi!
口開けて
（２人）あ～…
Open wide!
ハイパー・ウルトラ・
サディスティック・ミント　ほれ
Hyper-ultra-sadistic mints!
It hurts!
My mouth's numb.
かりゃい…
しびれるう～
What on earth are you doing?
何やってんだ？
Are you sure you'll be able to study?
本当に
勉強できるのか？
帰ったら
ちゃんと頑張るよ
I'll honestly do my best when I get home.
（カラスが鳴く）
Hey, 'Ma!
あッ　おばあちゃ～ん
ああ　唯ちゃん
Yui-chan!
I'm back from school.
ただいま～
お帰り
Welcome back.
はい　これ筑前煮
Here, I made some chicken stew.
I was just about to bring this over to you.
ちょうど
持っていくとこだったの
I made a lot, so please help yourself.
たくさん作ったから
みんなで　どうぞ
Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you for always- Oww!
いつも　すみませ…
あたッ！
What are you doing?
あら　何やってんの
てへへ…
You're still playing that...
それ　続けてるのね
え～と…
Gitah!
ギー太だよ！
そうそう　ギー太
Yes, Gitah!
Gitah, the guitar!
ギターのギー太だよ！
高校に入ってから
ずっとよねえ
You've been practicing ever
since you started high school.
唯ちゃん　ホントに頑張ってるのね
偉いねえ～
Yui-chan, you are such a hard worker.
I'm so happy for you.
へへへ…
She praised me...
褒められた～
She's always been taking good care of us...
お世話になってばっかりだな…
（ノック）
お姉ちゃん　ごはん
はッ！
Onee-chan, dinner's ready.
Oh, no! I only did my best practicing guitar!
ギターの練習　頑張ってしまった！
あむ…
おいしい！
ね～ッ
It's really good.
Yeah!
何か　お礼したいけど…
I wish I could do something for her.
I gave her some of the souvenirs you brought home last time.
お姉ちゃんの修学旅行の
お土産は　おすそ分けしといたよ
You're a great neighbor.
近所付き合い　上手！
そっかな～
Really?
また　クッキーでも焼いて
持っていこうかな
I guess I'll bake some cookies and give them to her.
Your homemade cookies?
憂のクッキー！
期末終わったらね
Once finals are done.
はうッ　う～…
頑張るって決めたんだもん
よし！
I'm going to study like mad!
Onee-chan-
お姉ちゃ…
あ～？
うん～？
・（梓）へえ　唯先輩
頑張ってるんだ
Wow, Yui-senpai's actually studying?
She stopped jogging after just one day, though.
ジョギングは
１日で挫折したけどね
（純）私　靴だけ買って
走んなかった
I bought jogging shoes but I don't even use them.
That's even worse.
（梓）それは
ダメダメ…
あ…
ね？
お～…
・（憂）でもね　ゆうべは
机で寝てたの
See?
But she fell asleep on her desk last night.
まあ　唯先輩だからね
Well, it's hard to change the fact that she's herself.
おお　バーゲンの季節だね！
Hey, the sales period's coming up!
Sales?
バーゲン？
季節の商品が　みんなみ～んな
All, I mean, all the seasonal merchandise becomes really, really cheap!
安くなるんだよ！
それはダイナミックね
Wow, that's amazing.
試験が終わったら
服買いに行きたいな～
I think I'll go shopping after finals.
それもいいな
お？
Sounds like a plan.
おお～！
どれもこれも
３０％引き　ムフー！
These are all 30% off!
微妙なセンスだな
おい…
Your fashion sense is also off.
う～…
・（憂）あッ！
うん？
どしたの？
お醤油　切れてた
What's wrong?
We're out of soy sauce.
買ってくるよ！
いいよ　私が行くから
I'll go get some.
It's okay, I'll go.
But you're in the middle of making dinner, aren't you?
憂　ごはん作ってる
途中でしょ
う～ん
スン　スン　スン…
Then can you make it quick?
じゃあ　なるべく
急いでもらっていい？
うん！
大丈夫？
Definitely.
Sure?
Yeah!
大丈夫～！
お醤油だからね！
Remember, soy sauce!
Soy sauce! Soy sauce! Soy sauce!
お醤油　お醤油　お醤油～
お塩じゃないよ　醤油だよ
Not salt, but soy sauce!
Not sauce, but soy sauce!
ソースじゃないよ　醤油だよ
砂糖じゃないよ…
・（とみ）あ　唯ちゃん
Not sugar, but-
Hey, Yui-chan.
Hey, 'Ma!
あッ　おばあちゃん
この間は　ごちそうさまでした
Thank you for sharing dinner with us last night.
はい　どうも
唯ちゃんは　これからお使い？
You're very welcome.
Are you going shopping?
お砂糖切らしてて～
あら　じゃあ…
We're short on sugar.
Oh, really?
Here you go.
Thank you!
はい
ありがとう
ちょうどよかった
唯ちゃんに　話があったのよ
What great timing.
I wanted to talk to you.
Look at this.
これなんだけどね
A talent contest?
演芸大会…？
Yes, it's held every year, but there aren't many contestants this year.
毎年やってるんだけど　今年は
出場者が少ないんですって
そうなんだ…
唯ちゃん　出てみない？
I see...
Yui-chan, are you interested?
えッ　私？
若い人が出ると
Me?
I think we'd all love to see young people there.
商店街の人たちも喜ぶと思うのよ
う～ん…
ギターのギー太
弾いてる唯ちゃん
I'd also love to see you play Gitah.
私も　見てみたいし
うふ…
日にちは？　はッ！
When is it?
〈期末が終わる次の日…！〉
It's the day right after finals...
あら　予定あった？
う　ううん！
Do you already have plans?
Not at all!
I wonder if Shige-san will come again this year.
今年も
しげさん出るかしら
いつもマジック
おもしろいんだけどねえ
His magic tricks are always so fun.
出よっかな…
I think... I'll go.
ホントに？
うん！
Really?
Yeah, I'll go!
私　出るよ！
あら　ありがとね　唯ちゃん
Oh...
Thank you, Yui-chan.
楽しみだねえ
唯ちゃんの晴れ姿
I can't wait to see you on stage.
Okay!
よし！
あ　そうそう
By the way, the winner gets a hot spring vacation.
優勝の商品ね　温泉旅行なの
憂ちゃんと行ったら？
Why don't you come with Ui-chan?
We weren't short on sugar, were we?
お砂糖じゃなかったね
うん…
No...
お醤油かけて食べたいよう…
I wish we had soy sauce.
ポン酢ならあるけど？
酸っぱいの　ダメだもん
We have ponzu.
I don't like sour stuff.
間違えるから…
Well, you're the one who forgot.
Should I go tell her that you won't be able to make it?
大会　断ってこようか？
お砂糖　返しにいくし
I need to return the sugar anyway.
ううん　おばあちゃん
すごく楽しみにしてるんだよ
Don't, she's really looking forward to it.
でも　期末の
次の日でしょう？
But it's right after finals.
練習とか　準備とか
大変なんじゃ…
How are you going to practice or prepare for it?
両方頑張るよ！
I'll manage both!
あ…　うん！
Good luck.
A talent contest?
演芸大会？
そう！
Yeah!
That sounds like fun.
おもしろそう
て　試験の翌日！
But it's right after finals.
だから　１人で出るよ
（３人）えッ？
That's why I'm going solo.
みんな　勉強あるだろうし
・（澪）お前もだろ
You guys are going to be busy studying.
Aren't you?
・（紬）ホントに
唯ちゃん１人で大丈夫？
Are you sure you can do it alone?
とにかく頑張るって決めたから
I decided that I'd do my best, after all!
つ～か　何で辞退しない？
Why didn't you just decline?
I wanted to make 'Ma next door happy.
お隣の　おばあちゃん
喜ばせたいんだよ
（紬）おばあちゃん？
'Ma?
She's always been taking care of us since we were little.
小さい頃から　お世話になっててね
恩返ししようかと…
I want to do something for her.
へ～…
私の晴れ姿　見たいって
She wants to see me perform.
優勝して
温泉旅行をプレゼントするんだ
I'm going to win and give her the hot springs vacation.
（３人）あ…
おばあちゃん…　何か
りっちゃんに　よく似てるんだよね
'Ma's kind of like you, Ricchan.
どこがだよ！
How?!
That's so wonderful.
素敵…　助けたカメに竜宮城とか
お地蔵さまに　かさとか
I've always loved stories like
Urashima Taro and Kasajizou.
そういうお話　大好き
（澪）昔話…？
Folktales?
頑張って　私に
できることがあったら手伝う！
Do your best.
I'll do anything I can help.
じゃあ　差し入れに
おいしいお菓子を…
Then can you bring some snacks?
（澪）おいおい
で　１人で何やんの？
Hey...
So what are you going to do?
演芸大会といったら…
A talent contest...
《はいはい　回るよ～》
Look, I'm spinning the plates!
て感じか？
違うよ
Something like that?
No!
ギターで　弾き語りしようと思って
I'm going to do a guitar solo.
唯のソロかあ
楽しみ～
You soloing, huh?
I'd like to see that.
ヘヘヘ～
ピン芸人デビューとはな
Your solo debut as a comedian, huh?
ボケたおして終わりそうだな
だから　演奏するんだよう
It'll probably just be Yui making funny comments.
Look, I'm playing my guitar!
・（体育教師）よ～い
Ready...
（体育教師が手をたたく）
A talent contest right after finals?
（梓）この時期に演芸大会？
余裕だね
She sounds confident.
何も考えてない
だけなんじゃ…
She's probably just not thinking straight.
お世話になってる　お隣の
おばあちゃんが推薦してくれて
Our neighbor next door who always takes good care of us asked her to do it.
え…
・（憂）お姉ちゃん張り切ってるの
My sister's really looking forward to it.
ふ～ん…　あッ
Really...
あッ
・（梓）唯先輩
うん？
Yui-senpai.
Oh, Azu-nyan.
あ　あずにゃん！
こんなところで練習ですか？
So you're practicing all the way out here.
I can't use the music room during the testing period,
試験前は
音楽室使えない規則だし
うちだと
憂の邪魔になるかなあって
and I don't want to disturb Ui at all.
あずにゃんは　お使い？
はい
Azu-nyan, did you go grocery shopping?
Yeah.
お醤油と　お砂糖は
間違えちゃダメだよ
Make sure you don't mistake soy sauce for sugar.
は？
ま　よくあることだけどね～
Well, it happens pretty often.
No, it doesn't.
ないです…
あ…
So are you really going to participate?
やっぱり　演芸大会
出るんですか？
あ　憂から聞いた？
はい
You heard from Ui?
Yeah.
う～　初めてのソロだからね
緊張するよ～
It'll be my first time soloing.
I'm so nervous.
１人で出るんですか？
そうだよ
Are you doing it alone?
Yup.
先輩たちは？
試験中だからね～
What about everyone else?
Well, they have finals to worry about.
迷惑かけちゃ
いけないと思って
I don't want to bother them.
大丈夫ですか？
うん
Will you be fine?
Yeah.
試験勉強もしながら？
頑張るよ～
But don't you have to study?
I'll do what I can.
あ　あ…
・（梓）わかりました
へ？
All right, then.
I'll do it with you.
私も　一緒に出ます
いいの？
Are you sure?
私　ふだんから
一応勉強してるので
I study on a daily basis, so I
think I'll do fine on my finals.
試験は大丈夫です…
と思います
Thank you, Azu-nyan!
ありがとう
あずにゃん！
In any case, we need to pick a song and practice.
とにかく
曲決めて　練習しないと
じゃあ　早速明日から
いいですね？
Well, let's start tomorrow.
Sounds good?
うん！
Yeah!
Azusa's going to do it?
（澪）梓が一緒に？
そう！
Yeah!
We were also talking about doing it, but...
やっぱ　私らも参加するかって
話してたんだけどな
２人のユニットも
いいわね
Seeing you two pair up would be nice for a change.
でへッ
・（梓）唯先輩
Yui-senpai!
あ　あずにゃん！
Azu-nyan!
やっほ～！
Hello!
う　うッ…
スケジュール立ててきました
I planned out your daily schedule.
まずは　図書館で勉強です
Studying at the library is up next.
あずにゃん
おやつの時間は…？
Azu-nyan, what about snack time?
No time for that.
ありません
あ～うう～！
Try to grab something during break.
（梓）休憩のとき
ササッと食べてください
梓ちゃん　頼もしい
Azusa-chan's so reliable.
We'll let her handle this.
今回は　梓に任せるか
うん
Yeah.
練習問題できました？
Have you solved the practice problems?
え？　あ　はい…
じゃあ　答え合わせ付き合います
Y-Yeah.
Then let's check answers.
あッ　え～と…
どうしたんですか？
But...
Is something wrong?
まじめにやってください
すみません…
Be serious.
I'm so sorry.
憂のお姉ちゃん
ホントおもしろいよね～
Ui, your sister's so interesting.
うん！
だから　毎日楽しいよ
Yeah, that's why every single day's so much fun.
First, let's pick a song.
（梓）まずは　何の曲を
演奏するかですよね
There's going to be a lot of old people.
お年寄りが
多いらしいよ
Then it must be enka, huh?
じゃあ　演歌？
うん！
Yeah.
・～ふわふわ
タ～アア～イム
Light and fluffy time!
その歌い方は…
コブシを回す練習だよ
I don't think that'd work.
We'll practice undulation.
「ふわふわ」の演歌バージョン？
あずにゃんも　やってみて
Light and Fluffy Time enka remix?
Azu-nyan, try it.
う　うう…
・～ふわふわ　タ～イム
Light and fluffy time...
コブシじゃなくて
体が回ってるよ
You're undulating your body, not your voice.
えッ　う…
・～ふわふわ
タ～イム
Light and fluffy time...
演歌の心には遠いなあ…
うッ
I don't think you're ready for enka.
すいません
演歌は無理です
I'm sorry.
I can't do enka.
じゃあ　民謡とか？
ロウソク？
Then how about a folk song?
A candle?
これの火を
消さずに歌うんだよ～
You have to sing without blowing the flame out.
What kind of practice is that?
何ですか？
その特訓…
じゃあ　いくよ
Okay, ready?
Lived a miner, forty-niner, and his daughter Clementine.
・～こきりこの竹は～
・～七寸五分じゃ～
こ…　こきりこ節ですか…
We're singing Clementine?
・～ま～どのサンサも…
Oh my darling, Oh my darling, Oh my darling...
ほれ　「デデレコデン」だよ
あずにゃん
Come on.
You sing the next bit, Azu-nyan.
えッ　う…
・～は～れのサンサも
You are lost and gone forever, dreadful sorry...
デデレコデン…
元気に！
Clementine...
With energy!
Oh my darling, Oh my darling, Oh my darling...
・～ま～どのサンサも
デデレコデン
もっと！
Clementine-
More energy!
You are lost and gone forever, dreadful sorry...
・～は～れのサンサも
デデレコデン！
Clementine!
いけるんじゃない？
自分を見失いそうです…
See, this'll work.
I'm going to lose myself.
Yui-chan!
・（とみ）唯ちゃ～ん
あ　うん？
あッ　おばあちゃん！
'Ma!
（とみ）はい　肉じゃがコロッケ
Here's some beef and potato croquettes.
わあ～！　ありがとう
Thank you so much!
憂ちゃんから
ここだって聞いたのよ
Ui-chan told me you'd be here.
練習　頑張ってるのねえ
そうなんだよ
I see you're practicing really hard.
Yup.
Oh, this is Azu-nyan, my partner.
あッ　一緒に出場してくれる
あずにゃん！
Nice to meet you.
初めまして
あらあら　そうなの
Oh, really?
あずにゃんさん　無理しないでね
Azunyan-san, don't overwork yourself.
はい
Thank you.
It's so good!
おいし～！
お隣のおばあちゃん
優しそうな方ですね
She's really kind.
うん　おばあちゃんの
炊き込みごはんとか
Yeah.
Her takikomi rice and tofu sushi are really good as well.
おいなりさんも　おいしいよ
You're like a stray cat that's being fed.
エサもらってる猫みたいですね
うう～ん～
We need to do our best.
でも　頑張らないとですね
そうだね
Yup.
ねえ　私たちのユニット名
何にする？
Hey, what should we call ourselves?
あ　「放課後ティータイム」じゃ
ないですもんね…
Right, we can't use Afterschool Tea Time.
「先輩後輩」とか？
それ　ことさら強調されるのも…
How about "SeniorJunior"?
There's no need to emphasize seniority...
う～ん…
「唯とあずにゃん」とか？
How about "Yui and Azu-nyan"?
あッ　「ゆいあず」って
どうですか？
Uh...
How about just YuiAzu?
おお　「ゆいあず」！
Yeah, YuiAzu!
それより　曲決めましょうよ
そうだね
Anyway, let's pick a song first.
Yeah.
What's a good song?
何がいいかなあ？
やっぱり「ふわふわ」が
I think light and fluffy is good.
いいんじゃないでしょうか？
・～ふわふわ…
Light and fluffy...
（さわ子）あ～…
What's wrong, Sawa-chan?
うッ　どうしたんだよ？
さわちゃん
I'm short on tea and sweets!
お茶とお菓子が
足りないのよ
Why don't we have tea parties anymore?!
何で　最近
お茶会しないのよ～
え…　だってテスト前だし
・（さわ子）それがどうしたの？
That's because we have finals coming up.
Who cares?
What's more important? Me or rules?
そんな規則と私
どっちが大事なの？
Rules, obviously.
うッ　そりゃ規則だろ
Sign: Final Exam - Japanese History B
ふ～　ふう…
（寝息）
・（和）先生！
わッ　う…
Miss!
May I pick up my eraser from the floor?
消しゴム落としたんで
拾っていいですか？
Yes, you may.
・（先生）どうぞ
うう…
ふう…
う　う～…
（三味線の音）
あ…
う　う～…
あッ？
こんなときに…
Sleeping now?
（寝息）
あ…
（鐘が３つ鳴る）
・（司会）ありがとう
ございました→
Thank you very much.
Next, number 14.
続きまして　１４番
「ゆいあず」のお二人です
The YuiAzu pair!
Yui-senpai! Yui-senpai!
唯先輩　唯先輩！
うん…？
出番ですよ
うん…　おおッ！
We're up.
（拍手）
こんにちは～！
桜ヶ丘高校３年の平沢唯です
Good afternoon!
I'm Hirasawa Yui, a senior at Sakuragaoka High!
I'm Nakano Azusa, a junior!
２年　中野梓です
２人合わせて
Put us together, and we're Yui-
Azu!
ゆい
あず
Enjoy!
で～す！　ジャン
Yui's just being her usual self.
唯は
いつもどおりだな
Azusa-chan looks a bit tensed.
梓ちゃん
顔こわばってる
私の方が緊張する…
Why am I the one nervous?
最初は　演歌やろうと思って
コブシを回す練習してたんですよ
At first, we thought about singing enka, so we practiced undulation!
そッ　そのコブシじゃな～い！
えッ？
No one cares about undulating your arm!
Azusa's adding in the comedic effects.
梓がつっこんでる…
仕込んできたな～
They came prepared.
私の方が先輩ですが
あずにゃんの方が
I'm older than her, but she's much more shrewd.
ちゃっかりしてるんですよ～
それを言うなら　しっかりだ～！
I think you mean responsible.
それじゃあ　いきますか
いきましょう
Well then, shall we go?
All right.
あれ～？
何やるんだっけ？
Wait, what were we going to do?
いい加減にしなさい
Enough with the jokes.
（男性）こりゃ　まいったなあ
That was good.
Now then, Brush and Ballpoint Pen, YuiAzu remix.
では　「ふでペン～ボールペン～」
ゆいあずバージョンです
１　２　３
One, two, three...
（民謡調で演奏する）
（３人）あ…
そうきたか
I wasn't expecting this...
まあ～　ウフフフ…
アハハハ…　まあ～
My brush, haha...
・～ふでペンＦＵ　ＦＵ
・～ふるえるＦＵ　ＦＵ
Is shaking, haha...
・～はじめてキミへの
ＧＲＥＥＴＩＮＧ　ＣＡＲＤ
This is my first greeting card to you.
・～ときめきＰＡＳＳＩＯＮ
あふれてＡＣＴＩＯＮ
My heart throbs with passion.
I'm overflowing with action.
・～はみだしちゃうかもね
So much that I might write off the paper.
（鐘が２つ鳴る）
・（司会）「ゆいあず」さん
ありがとうございました→
YuiAzu, thank you.
Next, we have Yoneyama Koutarou-san playing the bamboo flute!
次は　米山孝太郎さんによる
尺八の演奏です
参加賞でした
あら　私に？
We only got a participation prize.
Oh, for me?
ホントは旅行　プレゼント
したかったんだけど…
We wanted to get you the hot springs vacation.
ううん　気持ちだけで十分
ありがとう
No, it's the feeling that counts.
Thank you.
ホントに　２人とも
とっても素敵だったわ
You two did a great job.
Yui-chan, you've become so mature.
唯ちゃん
立派になっちゃって…　ねえ
あ…
えへへ…
・（とみ）そうそう　ちらし寿司
たくさん作ってあるのよ→
Oh, I made a lot of chirashizushi.
Let's fetch Ui-chan and have dinner together.
憂ちゃんや
皆さんと一緒に食べましょ
Yes! Azu-nyan, let's go!
わ～い　あずにゃん行こう
・（梓）はい！
Okay.
甘いシイタケ入ってる？
Did you add sweet mushrooms?
Yes, of course!
・（とみ）ええ　ええ　入ってるわよ
わ～い！
Yay!
Oh my god!
うおお～！
何だ？
What?
（律・澪・和・紬）うわッ！
You did really well!
（澪）高得点だらけ！
ど　どうしたんだ唯？
Wh-What happened, Yui?
ヤマが当たった～！
そんなとこだと思ったわ
I got lucky.
I figured it was something like that.
Well, you did your best studying.
でも　まあ
唯も頑張ったよ
そっかなあ…
私も演芸大会出たかった
You think so?
I wish I had been part of the contest.
じゃあ　今度は「ゆいむぎ」で！
Then we'll be YuiMugi next time!
「りつみお」でどうだ？
Whatcha think about RitsuMio?
「ゆいむぎみおあず」がいい
て　おい！
I think I like YuiMugiMioAzu.
Hey, what about me?!
やだ澪　やろうよ　やろうよ！
Come on, Mio! Let's do it!
No.
We can be Rittan-Mio-tan.
・（澪）やだ
「りったんみおたん」でいいから！
More so no.
Then how about...
・（澪）もっとやだ
・～
Deep, deep inside my heart,
there was a sanctuary where nothing ever resounded.
But now it's burning with heat, so I've forever changed.
I send out shockwaves to the world, as storms,
and tsunamis invite each other with the sound of rock and roll
to walk beside each other everywhere they go.
Whoops, I dropped my pick,
and I broke my drumstick, but hey it's all right.
I'm still a part of the usual sound,
which is actually quite miraculous!
We'll sing out loud to our hearts' content.
No matter how faint the song,
it's the one and only in the world.
We want to live our lives to the fullest
so that we won't care if we die today.
Let's play our passion to the world.
After all, this is our precious heartbeat.
We'll sing our treasured heartbeat.
So please listen!!
Preview
Finland this year...
What do you want? Why are you calling me after all these years?
No, could she really...
But wasn't she saying she's been single all this time?
I-I'm not interested in love at all!
Besides, my love right now is light music.
Sawa-chan's so popular.
Teacher!
I'm reluctant on asking her a favor now.